So we are going to show us doing this on a test net on Rinkeby.
现在我们要展示如何在测试网络  Rinkeby 上进行操作
But before we actually test it on Rinkeby,
但是在我们实际到 Rinkeby 上测试之前
I'm going to add a little bit of the auto verification piece in here as well,
我要在此处添加一些有关自动验证的内容
because we did that in the last lesson.
我们在上节课中也做过这个
And we wanted to show how to do it in hard hat deploy as well.
现在我们要展示一下如何在 "hardhat deploy" 中进行这个操作
So right after we deploy our Funmi, we can do something similar here,
因此，在我们部署过 "FundMe" 之后，我们可以做一些相似的事
we'll say, if developer chains includes network dot name,
我们之前写的是如果 `developmentChains` 包含 `network.name`
we'll say if developer chains doesn't include network dot name,
现在我们要写如果 `developmentChains` 不包含 `network.name`
because we don't want to verify on a local network.
因为我们不想在本地网络上进行验证
So we'll say if not development chains dot includes network dot name,
所以我们写下 `if(!developmentChains.includes(network.name))`
the exclamation mark, aka the bang
感叹号，或者说 "bang"
means not when we're talking about booleans.
表示布尔值中 "非"
So we're saying, if the name of the network isn't a development chain,
所以我们的意思就是，如果 `network` 的 `name` 不是一个 `developmentChains`
we want to go ahead and verify and same as last time.
我们就会继续并且进行验证，就和上次一样
And if process dot e NV dot ether scan API key,
并且，如果 `process.env.ETHERSCAN_API_KEY` 存在
then we're going to go ahead and verify.
我们就继续执行验证操作
Now before we had our verify code, right in our deploy code,
现在，在我们往部署代码中添加验证代码之前
we're gonna do something a little bit different here.
我们要做一点不同的事情
Instead of having our verify code in our deploy scripts here,
这次我们不再把验证代码放进我们的部署脚本中
we're actually going to create a new folder called utils, which stands for utilities.
而是创建一个新的文件夹，名为 "utils"，表示实用程序("utilities")
And this is where we're going to add different scripts that
我们要在这里添加一些不同的脚本
we can use across different deployments.
以便在不同的部署中使用
Because let's say we have 50 Deploy scripts,
假设我们有 50 个部署脚本
we're not going to make 50 Deploy functions,
我们不太可能去创建 50 个 "deploy" 函数
we're just going to add them to our utils folder,
更常用的方法是把它们放到 "utils" 文件夹中
and in our utils folder, or create a new file called verify dot j s,
在我们的 "utils" 文件夹中，我们要创建一个新文件名为 "verify.js"
we're going to add that code from our last project in here.
我们要把上一个项目中的代码添加过来
So if you want, you can go ahead copy paste from our last project over to this one,
如果你想的话，可以直接把上一个项目中的代码复制粘贴到这里
or you can pause the video to type it out yourself.
或者你可以暂停视频，手动输入代码
Since we're using the run command here, we're gonna do const run equals require RT hat.
由于我们在这里使用了 `run` 命令，所以我们添加 `const  = require("hardhat")`
And then at the bottom, we're going to do module exports. Exports equals verify.
而在底部，我们要添加 `module.exports = `
Now that we have a verify script in our utils folder,
现在我们就在 "utils" 文件夹中有了一个 "verify" 脚本了
back in our deploy Funmi we're going to say
回到我们的 "deploy-fund-me" 我们写下
const. Verify equals require dot dot slash utils. Slash verify.
`const  = require("../utils/verify")`
And since now in our verified Jas, we have a lot of this trycatch stuff in here,
由于我们的 "verify.js" 文件中有许多 `try-catch` 代码
we can just do a wait. Verify
所以我们可以使用 `await verify`
and a verify once again takes a contract address and a list of arguments.
`verify` 函数接收一个 `contractAddress` 和一个 `args` 列表
We'll say await verify, fund me dot address and then the list of arguments.
所以就是 `await verify(fundMe.address, )` 然后是 "args" 列表
To make the list of arguments easier to put in.
为了让我们的 "args" 列表更易输入
You can go const args, equals and then we'll just stick our eth USD price feed in here
你可以这样做 `const args = ` 然后我们直接把 `ethUsdPriceFeedAddress` 放到这里
and then replace this with args
接着把这里替换成 `args`
and then take this args and pop it on down into the second parameter here.
然后把 `args` 放到这里，作为它的第二个参数
All right, great.
干的非常好